<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Razer Insure</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_browse">Browse</string>
    <string name="title_search">Search</string>
    <string name="title_account">Account</string>
    <string name="title_account_overview">Account Overview</string>
    <string name="saved_card_description">This is a picture of a credit card</string>
    <string name="title_saved_cards">Saved Cards</string>
    <string name="title_activity_payment">PaymentActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="title_add_new_card">+ Add New Card</string>
    <string name="title_plan_selected">This is a selected insurance plan</string>
    <string name="title_plan_selected_header">Plan Selected</string>
    <string name="title_amount_to_be_deducted_header">Amount to be deducted</string>
    <string name="title_coverage_header">Coverage</string>
    <string name="coverage_option_description">A coverage option</string>
    <string name="title_terms_and_conditions_header">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="title_terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions here</string>
    <string name="checkout_button_text">Checkout</string>
    <string name="pay_now_button_text">Pay Now</string>
    <string name="insurance_1_title">Insurance 1</string>
    <string name="insurance_1_details">This is insurance 1</string>
    <string name="insurance_2_title">Insurance 2</string>
    <string name="insurance_2_details">This is insurance 2</string>
    <string name="insurance_3_title">Insurance 3</string>
    <string name="insurance_3_details">This is insurance 3</string>
    <string name="insurance_4_title">Insurance 4</string>
    <string name="insurance_4_details">This is insurance 4</string>
    <string name="debit_card">Debit Card</string>
    <string name="credit_card">Credit Card</string>
    <string name="overflow_help">Help</string>
    <string name="insurance_plan_default_title">title</string>
    <string name="default_number">999,999</string>
    <string name="default_amount_type">Current Balance</string>
    <string name="default_amount_suffix">Razer Gold</string>
    <string name="add">+</string>
    <string name="dinosaur_text">People your age usually goes for\n Endowment Plans.\n New? Let me guide you!</string>
    <string name="get_insurance">Get Insurance</string>
    <string name="save_a_copy">Save a copy\nof your family\'s insurance</string>
    <string name="endowment_plans_title">Endowment\nPlans</string>
    <string name="car_insurance_title">Car\nInsurance</string>
    <string name="travel_insurance_title">Travel\nInsurance</string>
    <string name="more_options_title">More\nOptions</string>

    <string name="title_question">What is it?</string>
    <string name="dinosaur_text_insurance_plan">Hey Jolyn, Just swipe these cards left\nto read more about what an\nEndowment Plan is</string>
    <string name="default_statistics">73%</string>
    <string name="default_statistics_rest">of your friend in Razer have bought\nthis plan. Here are some of your peers\nwho are open to sharing:</string>
    <string name="title_policy_overview">Overall policy plans</string>
    <string name="default_number_of_current_policies_1">2</string>
    <string name="current_policy_shown_1">Travel Plans</string>
    <string name="default_number_of_current_policies_2">1</string>
    <string name="current_policy_shown_2">Endowment Plan</string>
    <string name="current_policies">Current policies</string>
    <string name="travel_plan_details_header">Travel Plan Details</string>
    <string name="reward_profile_level_text">Level 3</string>
    <string name="my_badges_header_text">My Badges</string>
    <string name="my_vouchers_header_texts">My Vouchers</string>
    <string name="travel_plan_introduction">We looked into the finer details of the plan and figured out what works best for you. Thank us later! Also, please let us know how we can improve.</string>
    <string name="exp_bar_header_text">EXP to next level: 0/1000</string>
    <string name="welcome_back_text">Welcome back, User!</string>
    <string name="travel_plans_header">Travel Plans</string>
    <string name="travel_plans_description_header_text">Trip Details</string>
    <string name="travel_plans_description_header_body">Policy Type: Single</string>
    <string name="travel_plans_description_header_body2">Who\'s going: Only Me</string>
    <string name="travel_plans_description_header_body3">Destination: Malaysia</string>
    <string name="travel_plans_description_header_body4">Start Date: 05/05/2019</string>
    <string name="travel_plans_description_header_body5">End Date: 05/05/2020</string>
    <string name="travel_plan_selection_button_text">Select Travel Plan</string>
    <string name="title_activity_travel_plans">TravelPlansActivity</string>
    <string name="travel_plan_description">This is a travel plan</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_agree_text">I hereby agree to the terms and conditions stated above.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_body">"GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS  As with any insurance policy, there are reciprocal rights and obligations. It is governed by the French Insurance Code. These rights and obligations are explained in the pages that follow.   PROVISIONS COMMON TO ALL COVERAGE   DEFINITIONS   Risk: unintentional, unforeseeable, unavoidable and external event.   Insured The persons duly insured under this policy hereinafter referred by the term \"you\".   Insurer / Provider FWD Insurance hereafter referred to as \"we\", whose headquarters is located at:   FDW Insurance Singapore  6 Temasek Blvd, #18-01 Suntec Tower,  Four 038986  Attack / Acts of terrorism  Attack refers to any act of violence, constituting a criminal or illegal attack, made against persons and/or property, in the country in which you are staying, the purpose of which is to seriously disturb public order. This attack will be recorded by the French Ministry of Foreign Affairs.   Natural disasters  The abnormal intensity of a natural agent not arising from human intervention.   Insurance Code Collection of legislative and regulatory texts which govern the insurance policy.   Home address  Home address refers to your main and usual place of residence; your home address must be in Europe.   DROM POM COM (FRENCH OVERSEAS TERRITORIES)  DROM POM COM refers to the new designations of DOM TOM since the Constitutional Reform of 17 March 2003, arising from change in the DOM TOM names and their definitions.   Transport company  Transport company refers to any company duly approved by the public authorities for the transporting of passengers.  Europe \"Europe\" refers to the countries of the European Union, Switzerland, Norway or the Principality of Monaco.   Excess  Part of the compensation that you are responsible for.   Mainland France  Mainland France refers to: mainland France and Corsica, including the DROM POM COM (new DOM TOM names since the constitutional reform of 17 March 2003).   Insurance claims management agency   GRITCHEN AFFINITY  Rue Charles Durand BP 66048  18024 BOURGES, FRANCE Cedex   Strike  A collective action consisting in a concerted cessation of work by the employees of a company, an economic sector or a professional category aimed at support claims.   Civil war  Civil war refers to the armed opposition of several parties belonging to the same country, as well as any armed rebellion, revolution, sedition, insurrection, coup, application of martial law or closure of the borders controlled by the local authorities.   Foreign war  Foreign war refers to the armed opposition declared or not by one State to another State, as well as any invasion or state of siege.   Illness / Accident  Any deterioration in health detected by a medical authority, requiring medical care and the absolute cessation of any professional or other activities.   Family member  Family member is defined as any person that can prove a family relationship (by law or by fact) to the insured.  Pollution: Environmental degradation by introducing substances not naturally present in the environment into the air, water or soil.   Usual residence  The policyholder's usual residence refers to their place of residence for tax purposes; your main residence must be located in Europe.   Claim  Event likely to lead to the application of the policy’s cover.   Subscriber  The policyholder, natural or legal person who takes out the insurance policy. Subrogation The legal situation through which a person transfers the rights of any other person (including: substituting the Insurer for the Policyholder for prosecution purposes against the opposing party).   Third party:  Any person other than the Insured liable for damage. Any Insured who is a victim of consequential bodily, material or immaterial injury caused by another Insured (the Insured are regarded as third parties in respect of each other).   WHAT IS THE GEOGRAPHICAL COVERAGE OF THE POLICY?   The coverage and/or benefits contained in this policy shall apply worldwide.   WHAT IS THE POLICY TERM?   The validity period corresponds to the duration of the services sold by the trip organiser. In any case the cover period may not exceed 3 months from the trip departure day.   The \"CANCELLATION\" coverage shall take effect on the date of subscription to this policy and shall expire on the trip departure day (outbound journey).   WHAT ARE THE GENERAL EXCLUSIONS APPLICABLE TO ALL OF OUR COVERAGE?   We cannot intervene when your coverage or benefit requests are the result of damage resulting from:  . Epidemics, natural disasters and pollution;  . Civil or foreign war, a riot, popular movement or strike;  . The voluntary participation of an insured person in riots or strikes;  . The release of nuclear radiation or any radiation from ionising radiation;  . Alcoholism, drunkenness, drug use, narcotics, drugs not medically prescribed;  . Any intentional act which may trigger the policy coverage and any consequences of a criminal procedure which you are involved in;  . Fights, bets, crimes, brawls (except self-defence);  . Engaging in the following sports: bob-sleigh, skeleton, mountaineering, luge competition, aviation sports with the exception of parasailing as well as those resulting from participation or training in official matches or competitions, organised by a sports federation;  . Suicide and the consequences of suicide attempts;  . Lack of uncertainty.   HOW IS YOUR COMPENSATION CALCULATED?   If the compensation cannot be determined by mutual agreement, it is evaluated by an amicable expert, subject to our respective rights.   We each choose our own expert. If these experts do not agree, they will call on a third expert and all three will work together and by a majority of votes.   If one of us fails to appoint an expert or the two experts fail to agree on the choice of a third expert, the appointment shall be made by the President of the High Court, in summary proceedings. Each co-contracting party shall bear the costs and fees of their expert, and if applicable, half of those of the third expert.   HOW SOON WILL YOU BE COMPENSATED?  The settlement will take place within a period of fifteen days from the agreement between us, or from the notification of the enforceable judicial decision.   WHAT PENALTIES APPLY IN THE EVENT OF AN INTENTIONAL FALSE DECLARATION MADE BY YOU AT THE TIME OF THE CLAIM?  Any fraud, non-disclosure or intentional false declaration made by you about the circumstances or consequences of a claim will result in the loss of any entitlement to a benefit or compensation for this claim.   WHAT ARE THE CLAIM REVIEW PROCEDURES?  In the event of difficulties, you must send your claim to:   FDW Insurance Singapore  6 Temasek Blvd, #18-01 Suntec Tower,  Four 038986  Lastly, if you are not satisfied by the answer provided, you may request the opinion of the Ombudsman under the terms which you will be notified of after sending a request to the above address.     AUTHORITY RESPONSIBLE FOR OVERSEEING THE INSURANCE COMPANY  L’Autorité de Contrôle Prudentiel  61 rue Taitbout 75436 PARIS, FRANCE CEDEX 09   POLICYHOLDER'S INFORMATION ON THE PROVISIONS OF THE NATIONAL COMMISSION FOR COMPUTING AND FREEDOM-CNIL   Personal information is processed in compliance with the law on computing and freedom of 6 January 1978, as amended. Its processing is necessary to manage the policy and it coverage. It is intended for the broker, the insurer, their agents and subcontractors, reinsurers as well as for professional bodies in the context of the legal provisions and regulations.   The policyholder has the right to access, amend and refuse by sending an email to relationconsommateurs@allianz.fr or a letter to Allianz - Service des relations avec les consommateurs - TSA 21017 - 92099 La Défense, France Cedex.   SUBROGATION   After having paid you compensation, with the exception of that paid under the Travel Accidents cover, we are subrogated in the rights and actions that you can have against the third party responsible for the accident, as provided for in Art. L. 121-12 of the French Insurance Code.   Our subrogation is limited to the amount of compensation that we have paid you or the services that we have provided.   WHAT IS THE LIMITATION PERIOD?   Any action relating to this policy may only be exercised within a period of two years from the date of the event which caused it according to the conditions determined by Articles L.114-1 and L.114-2 of the French Insurance Code.   WHAT ARE THE LIMITS APPLICABLE IN CASES OF FORCE MAJEURE?  We cannot be held responsible for shortcomings in the implementation of the Assistance benefits resulting from cases of force majeure or from the following events: civil or foreign wars, known political instability, popular movements, riots, acts of terrorism, retaliation, a restriction on the free movement of persons and goods, strikes, explosions, natural disasters, release of nuclear radiation, or from the delays in the implementation of benefits resulting from the same causes.  "</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_policies">activity_my_policies</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_claim_process">claim_process</string>
    <string name="icon_with_select_button_text">Insert text here</string>
    <string name="razor_pay">Razer Pay</string>
    <string name="razer_coin">Razer Coins</string>
</resources>
